A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.1, Series 300 Latin America - Series 833 Lebanon FA386b
Rockefeller Archive Center
- England, 1919-1960; 401; 10.4 Cubic Feet; 83 __Boxes __10.4 cubic feet
  - England - Medical Sciences, 401.A
    - Royal Society of Medicine - Medical Library, 1944-1951 (Box 25, Folder 326)
    - Royal Society of Medicine - Medical Library, 1944-1951 (Box 25, Folder 327)
    - Royal Society of Medicine - Medical Library, 1944-1951 (Box 25, Folder 328)
    - St. Bartholomew's Hospital - Endocrinology, 1939-1942 (Box 26, Folder 329)
    - St. Bartholomew's Hospital - Endocrinology, 1939-1942 (Box 26, Folder 330)
    - St. Bartholomew's Hospital - Garrod, Lawrence P. - (Visit, Bacteriology) Endocrinology, 1939-1942 (Box 26, Folder 331)
    - St. Bartholomew's Hospital - Pediatrics, 1927-1934 (Box 26, Folder 332)
    - St. Thomas's Hospital - Medical School - Clinical Laboratory, 1923-1926, 1947-1948 (Box 26, Folder 333)
    - St. Thomas's Hospital - Medical School - Clinical Laboratory, 1923-1926, 1947-1948 (Box 26, Folder 334)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1927, 1929-1945 (Box 26, Folder 335)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1927, 1929-1945 (Box 26, Folder 336)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1927, 1929-1945 (Box 26, Folder 337)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1927, 1929-1945 (Box 26, Folder 338)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1927, 1929-1945 (Box 26, Folder 339)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1927, 1929-1945 (Box 26, Folder 340)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1927, 1929-1945 (Box 26, Folder 341)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1927, 1929-1945 (Box 26, Folder 342)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1927, 1929-1945 (Box 26, Folder 343)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1927, 1929-1945 (Box 26, Folder 344)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1946-1958 (Box 27, Folder 345)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1946-1958 (Box 27, Folder 346)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1946-1958 (Box 27, Folder 347)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1946-1958 (Box 27, Folder 348)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1946-1958 (Box 27, Folder 349)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1946-1958 (Box 27, Folder 350)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1946-1958 (Box 27, Folder 351)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1946-1958 (Box 27, Folder 352)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1946-1958 (Box 27, Folder 353)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry), 1946-1958 (Box 27, Folder 354)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry) - Report and Pamphlets, 1936-1941; 4 items (Box 27, Folder 355)
    - Tavistock Square Clinic - (Psychiatry) - Reports, 1946-1949; 14 items (Box 27, Folder 356)
    - University of Birmingham - Commission - (Visit, Pathology), 1930-1931 (Box 28, Folder 357)
    - University of Birmingham - Commission - (Visit, Pathology), 1930-1931 (Box 28, Folder 358)
    - University of Birmingham - Medical Center, 1926-1927, 1929-1933 (Box 28, Folder 359)
    - University of Birmingham - Medical Center, 1926-1927, 1929-1933 (Box 28, Folder 360)
    - University of Birmingham - Medical Center, 1926-1927, 1929-1933 (Box 28, Folder 361)
    - University of Cambridge - Adrian, E. D. - (Visit, Physiology), 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 362)
    - University of Cambridge - Adrian, E. D. - (Visit, Physiology), 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 363)
    - University of Cambridge - Brain Injuries Research, 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 364)
    - University of Cambridge - Brain Injuries Research, 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 365)
    - University of Cambridge - Experimental Medicine, 1929-1940, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 366)
    - University of Cambridge - Experimental Medicine, 1929-1940, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 367)
    - University of Cambridge - Experimental Medicine, 1929-1940, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 368)
    - University of Cambridge - Krebs, H. A. - (Refugee, Pharmacology), 1933-1935 (Box 28, Folder 369)
    - University of Cambridge - Laser, Hans - (Refugee, Physiology), 1933-1936 (Box 28, Folder 370)
    - University of Cambridge - Pathology - Historical Record - UC P, 1922-1937 (Box 29, Folder 371)
    - University of Cambridge - Pharmacology - (Refugee, Vogt, Marthe), 1931-1941 (Box 29, Folder 372)
    - University College, London - Anatomy, 1923-1936 (Box 29, Folder 373)
    - University College, London - (Anatomy, Pharmacology, Physiology), 1920-1927, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 374)
    - University College, London - (Anatomy, Pharmacology, Physiology), 1920-1927, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 375)
    - University College, London - (Anatomy, Pharmacology, Physiology), 1920-1927, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 376)
    - University College, London - (Anatomy, Pharmacology, Physiology), 1920-1927, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 377)
    - University College, London - Clinical Medicine, 1929-1944 (Box 29, Folder 378)
    - University College, London - Clinical Medicine, 1929-1944 (Box 29, Folder 379)
    - University College, London - Haber, Rudolf - (Refugee, Physiology), 1933-1934 (Box 29, Folder 380)
    - University College, London - Hospital Medical School - Indenture, 1920 (Box 29, Folder 381)
    - University College, London - Pediatrics, 1923-1932 (Box 30, Folder 382)
    - University College, London - Pharmacology - (Refugee, Krayer, Otto), 1933-1936 (Box 30, Folder 383)
    - University College, London - Physiology, 1923-1941 (Box 30, Folder 384)
    - University College, London - Physiology, 1923-1941 (Box 30, Folder 385)
    - University College, London - Physiology, 1923-1941 (Box 30, Folder 386)
    - University College, London - Physiology, 1923-1941 (Box 30, Folder 387)
    - University College, London - Pilchen, R. S. - (Visit, Surgery), 1949 (Box 30, Folder 388)
    - University College, London - Young, J. Z. - (Visit, Anatomy), 1949 (Box 30, Folder 389)
    - University of Leeds - Medical Faculty, 1926-1931 (Box 30, Folder 390)
    - University of London - (Appropriations), 1920-1933 and Undated Material (Box 30, Folder 391)
    - University of London, 1920-1921 (Box 30, Folder 392)
    - University of London, 1920-1921 (Box 30, Folder 393)
    - University of London, 1920-1921 (Box 30, Folder 394)
    - University of London, 1920-1921 (Box 30, Folder 395)
    - University of London, 1920-1921 (Box 30, Folder 396)
    - University of London, 1920-1921 (Box 30, Folder 397)
    - University of London, 1920-1921 (Box 30, Folder 398)
    - University of London, 1922-1941, 1948-1962 (Box 31, Folder 399)
    - University of London, 1922-1941, 1948-1962 (Box 31, Folder 400)
    - University of London, 1922-1941, 1948-1962 (Box 31, Folder 401)
    - University of London, 1922-1941, 1948-1962 (Box 31, Folder 402)
    - University of London, 1922-1941, 1948-1962 (Box 31, Folder 403)
    - University of London, 1922-1941, 1948-1962 (Box 31, Folder 404)
    - University of London, 1922-1941, 1948-1962 (Box 31, Folder 405)
    - University of London, 1922-1941, 1948-1962 (Box 31, Folder 406)
    - University of London - Reports, 1920-1934; 18 items (Box 31, Folder 407)
    - University of London - Land Purchase, 1926-1938, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 408)
    - University of London - Land Purchase, 1926-1938, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 409)
    - University of London - Land Purchase, 1926-1938, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 410)
    - University of London - Land Purchase, 1926-1938, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 411)
    - University of London - Land Purchase, 1926-1938, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 412)
    - University of London - Land Purchase - Pamphlets, 1932-1933; 3 items (Box 32, Folder 413)
    - University of Manchester - Deutsch, Walter - (Refugee, Physiology), 1933-1934 (Box 32, Folder 414)
    - University of Manchester - Jefferson, Geoffrey - (Visit, Neurosurgery), 1943-1944 (Box 32, Folder 415)
    - University of Manchester - Prausnitz, Carl - (Refugee Hygiene), 1933-1936 (Box 32, Folder 416)
    - VIS "Visits to the United States by Medical Scientists" - Medical Education - England - Historical Record, 1920-1929 (Box 32, Folder 417)
  - England - Nursing, 401.C
    - (Nursing), 1922-1940 (Box 33, Folder 419)
    - (Nursing), 1922-1940 (Box 33, Folder 420)
    - (Nursing), 1922-1940 (Box 33, Folder 421)
    - (Nursing), 1922-1940 (Box 33, Folder 422)
    - (Nursing), 1922-1940 (Box 33, Folder 423)
    - (Nursing), 1922-1940 (Box 33, Folder 424)
    - (Nursing) - Reports, 1922-1927; 2 items (Box 33, Folder 425)
    - BEA-1 Beard, Mary - "Study Maternal Care in England", 1925 (Box 33, Folder 426)
    - CRO-1 Crowell, F. Elisabeth "Memorandum: Study of Sick Nursing and Health Visiting in England", 1922 (Box 34, Folder 427)
    - St. Thomas Hospital - School of Nursing, 1926-1929 (Box 34, Folder 428)
    - University College - (Hospital, London), 1920-1930 (Box 34, Folder 429)
    - University College - (Hospital, London), 1920-1930 (Box 34, Folder 430)
  - England - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 401.D
    - Agricultural Research Council - Quastel, Juda H. - (Soil Enzyme Chemistry), 1942-1945 (Box 34, Folder 431)
    - Agricultural Research Council - Quastel, Juda H. - (Soil Enzyme Chemistry), 1942-1945 (Box 34, Folder 432)
    - Armstrong College - Physics, 1931-1932 (Box 34, Folder 433)
    - Birkbeck College - Booth, Andrew D. - (X-Ray Crystallography), 1946-1948 (Box 34, Folder 434)
    - Birkbeck College - Botany, 1934-1945 (Box 34, Folder 435)
    - Birkbeck College - Botany, 1934-1945 (Box 34, Folder 436)
    - Frankel, G. - (Zoology-Entomology), 1946-1947 (Box 34, Folder 437)
    - Huxley, Julian - (Visit, Wartime Research), 1939-June 1940 (Box 34, Folder 438)
    - Huxley, Julian - (Visit, Wartime Research), 1939-June 1940 (Box 34, Folder 439)
    - Huxley, Julian - (Visit, Wartime Research), 1939-June 1940 (Box 34, Folder 440)
    - Huxley, Julian - (Visit, Wartime Research), 1939-June 1940 (Box 34, Folder 441)
    - Huxley, Julian - (Visit, Wartime Research), July 1940-1941 (Box 35, Folder 442)
    - Huxley, Julian - (Visit, Wartime Research), July 1940-1941 (Box 35, Folder 443)
    - Huxley, Julian - (Visits, Wartime Research) - Reports, 1939-1940; 3 items (Box 35, Folder 444)
    - Huxley, Julian - (Visit, Evolutionary Biology), 1953-1957 (Box 35, Folder 445)
    - Huxley, Julian - (Visit, Evolutionary Biology), 1953-1957 (Box 35, Folder 446)
    - Imperial College of Science and Technology - Astrophysics, 1937-1940 (Box 35, Folder 447)
    - Imperial College of Science and Technology - Paneth, Fritz - (Refugee, Physical Chemistry), 1933-1934 (Box 35, Folder 448)
    - John Innes Horticultural Institution - Cytology, 1938-1941 (Box 35, Folder 449)
    - London Hospital - Spectrophotometry, 1945-1947 (Box 35, Folder 450)
    - Marine Biological Association - Laboratory, 1930-1948 (Box 35, Folder 451)
    - Marine Biological Association - Laboratory, 1930-1948 (Box 35, Folder 452)
    - Marine Biological Association - Laboratory, 1930-1948 (Box 35, Folder 453)
    - Marine Biological Association - Laboratory - Reports, 1928-1937, 1944; 5 items (Box 35, Folder 454)
    - Middlesex Hospital - Biology, 1935-1936 (Box 36, Folder 455)
    - National Institute for Medical Research - Biochemistry, 1943-1944 (Box 36, Folder 456)
    - Oxford University - Biochemistry, 1936-1958 (Box 36, Folder 457)
    - Oxford University - Biochemistry, 1936-1958 (Box 36, Folder 458)
    - Oxford University - Biochemistry, 1936-1958 (Box 36, Folder 459)
    - Oxford University - Biochemistry, 1936-1958 (Box 36, Folder 460)
    - Oxford University - Biochemistry, 1936-1958 (Box 36, Folder 461)
    - Oxford University - Biochemistry, 1936-1958 (Box 36, Folder 462)
    - Oxford University - Biochemistry, 1936-1958 (Box 36, Folder 463)
    - Oxford University - Biochemistry, 1936-1958 (Box 36, Folder 464)
    - Oxford University - Biochemistry, 1936-1958 (Box 36, Folder 465)
    - Oxford University - Biochemistry, 1936-1958 (Box 36, Folder 466)
    - Oxford University - Biochemistry, 1936-1958 (Box 36, Folder 467)
    - Oxford University - Biochemistry, 1936-1958 (Box 36, Folder 468)
    - Oxford University - Biochemistry, 1936-1958 (Box 36, Folder 469)
    - Oxford University - Biochemistry - Supplementary Material, 1940-1944; 4 items (Box 36, Folder 470)
    - Oxford University - Chemistry, 1933-1958 (Box 37, Folder 471)
    - Oxford University - Chemistry, 1933-1958 (Box 37, Folder 472)
    - Oxford University - Chemistry, 1933-1958 (Box 37, Folder 473)
    - Oxford University - Chemistry, 1933-1958 (Box 37, Folder 474)
    - Oxford University - Chemistry, 1933-1958 (Box 37, Folder 475)
    - Oxford University - Chemistry, 1933-1958 (Box 37, Folder 476)
    - Oxford University - Chemistry, 1933-1958 (Box 37, Folder 477)
    - Oxford University - Chemistry, 1933-1958 (Box 37, Folder 478)
    - Oxford University - Chemistry, 1933-1958 (Box 37, Folder 479)
    - Oxford University - Chemistry - Report, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 480)
    - Oxford University - Chemistry - Report, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 481)
    - Oxford University - Chemistry - Report, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 482)
    - Oxford University - Chemistry - Report, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 483)
    - Oxford University - Chemistry - Report, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 484)
    - Oxford University - Physics, 1933-1941 (Box 37, Folder 485)
    - Oxford University - Protein Research, 1940-1964 (Box 38, Folder 486)
    - Oxford University - Protein Research, 1940-1964 (Box 38, Folder 487)
    - Oxford University - Protein Research, 1940-1964 (Box 38, Folder 488)
    - Oxford University - Protein Research, 1940-1964 (Box 38, Folder 489)
    - Oxford University - Protein Research, 1940-1964 (Box 38, Folder 490)
    - Oxford University - Protein Research, 1940-1964 (Box 38, Folder 491)
    - Oxford University - Protein Research, 1940-1964 (Box 38, Folder 492)
    - Oxford University - Protein Research, 1940-1964 (Box 38, Folder 493)
    - Oxford University - Protein Research - Reports, 1942; 2 items (Box 38, Folder 494)
    - Oxford University - Schrodinger, Erwin - (Refugee, Physics), 1933-1934 (Box 38, Folder 495)
    - Oxford University - Sutton, Leslie E. - (Visit, Chemistry), 1946-1947 (Box 38, Folder 496)
    - Oxford University - Theoretical Biology, 1935-1936 (Box 38, Folder 497)
    - Oxford University - Theoretical Biology, 1935-1936 (Box 38, Folder 498)
    - Oxford University - Theoretical Biology, 1937-1942 (Box 39, Folder 499)
    - Oxford University - Theoretical Biology, 1937-1942 (Box 39, Folder 500)
    - Oxford University - Theoretical Biology, 1937-1942 (Box 39, Folder 501)
    - Oxford University - Theoretical Biology, 1937-1942 (Box 39, Folder 502)
    - Oxford University - Thompson, H. W. - (Visit, Chemistry), 1948-1950 (Box 39, Folder 503)
    - Oxford University - Zoology, 1934-1945 (Box 39, Folder 504)
    - Oxford University - Zoology, 1934-1945 (Box 39, Folder 505)
    - Oxford University - Zoology, 1934-1945 (Box 39, Folder 506)
    - Polanyi, M. - (Visit, Physics), 1946 (Box 39, Folder 507)
    - Rothamsted Experimental Station - Physiology, 1939-1947 (Box 39, Folder 508)
    - Rothamsted Experimental Station - Physiology, 1939-1947 (Box 39, Folder 509)
    - Rothamsted Experimental Station - Physiology, 1939-1947 (Box 39, Folder 510)
    - Royal Institution of Great Britain, 1929-1934, 1947-1960 (Box 40, Folder 511)
    - Royal Institution of Great Britain, 1929-1934, 1947-1960 (Box 40, Folder 512)
    - Royal Institution of Great Britain, 1929-1934, 1947-1960 (Box 40, Folder 513)
    - Royal Institution of Great Britain, 1929-1934, 1947-1960 (Box 40, Folder 514)
    - Royal Institution of Great Britain, 1929-1934, 1947-1960 (Box 40, Folder 515)
    - Royal Institution of Great Britain, 1929-1934, 1947-1960 (Box 40, Folder 516)
    - Royal Institution of Great Britain, 1929-1934, 1947-1960 (Box 40, Folder 517)
    - Royal Society, London - Scientific Journals, 1940-1945 (Box 40, Folder 518)
    - Royal Society, London - Scientific Journals, 1940-1945 (Box 40, Folder 519)
    - Royal Society, London - Scientific Journals, 1940-1945 (Box 40, Folder 520)
    - Royal Society, London - Scientific Journals - Accounts, 1942-1945 (Box 41, Folder 521)
    - Strangeways Research Laboratory, 1934-1965 (Box 41, Folder 522)
    - Strangeways Research Laboratory, 1934-1965 (Box 41, Folder 523)
    - Strangeways Research Laboratory, 1934-1965 (Box 41, Folder 524)
    - Strangeways Research Laboratory, 1934-1965 (Box 41, Folder 525)
    - Strangeways Research Laboratory, 1934-1965 (Box 41, Folder 526)
    - Strangeways Research Laboratory, 1934-1965 (Box 41, Folder 527)
    - Strangeways Research Laboratory, 1934-1965 (Box 41, Folder 528)
    - Strangeways Research Laboratory, 1934-1965 (Box 41, Folder 529)
    - Tilley, C. E. - (Experimental Minerology), 1932 (Box 41, Folder 530)
    - University of Birmingham - Physiology, 1941-1945 (Box 41, Folder 531)
    - University of Birmingham - Physiology, 1941-1945 (Box 41, Folder 532)
    - University of Bristol - Physics, 1929-1938, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 533)
    - University of Bristol - Physics, 1929-1938, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 534)
    - University of Bristol - Physics, 1929-1938, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 535)
    - University of Bristol - Physics - Reports, 1927-1929; 6 items (Box 41, Folder 536)
    - University of Cambridge - Biochemistry, 1935-1941, 1943-1959 (Box 42, Folder 537)
    - University of Cambridge - Biochemistry, 1935-1941, 1943-1959 (Box 42, Folder 538)
    - University of Cambridge - Biochemistry, 1935-1941, 1943-1959 (Box 42, Folder 539)
    - University of Cambridge - Biochemistry, 1935-1941, 1943-1959 (Box 42, Folder 540)
    - University of Cambridge - Biochemistry, 1935-1941, 1943-1959 (Box 42, Folder 541)
    - University of Cambridge - Biochemistry, 1935-1941, 1943-1959 (Box 42, Folder 542)
    - University of Cambridge - Biochemistry, 1935-1941, 1943-1959 (Box 42, Folder 543)
    - University of Cambridge - Biochemistry, 1935-1941, 1943-1959 (Box 42, Folder 544)
    - University of Cambridge - Biochemistry, 1935-1941, 1943-1959 (Box 42, Folder 545)
    - University of Cambridge - Biology and Parasitology, 1934-1944 (Box 42, Folder 546)
    - University of Cambridge - Biology and Parasitology, 1934-1944 (Box 42, Folder 547)
    - University of Cambridge - Biology and Parasitology, 1934-1944 (Box 42, Folder 548)
    - University of Cambridge - Biology and Parasitology, 1934-1944 (Box 42, Folder 549)
    - University of Cambridge - Biology and Parasitology, 1945-1955 (Box 43, Folder 550)
    - University of Cambridge - Biology and Parasitology, 1945-1955 (Box 43, Folder 551)
    - University of Cambridge - Biology and Parasitology, 1945-1955 (Box 43, Folder 552)
    - University of Cambridge - Born, Max - (Refugee, Physics), 1933-1935 (Box 43, Folder 553)
    - University of Cambridge - Courant, Richard - (Refugee, Mathematics), 1933 (Box 43, Folder 554)
    - University of Cambridge - Embryology, 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 555)
    - University of Cambridge - Embryology, 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 556)
    - University of Cambridge - Fajans, K. - (Refugee, Chemistry), 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 557)
    - University of Cambridge - Klemperer, Otto - (Refugee, Physics), 1933 (Box 43, Folder 558)
    - University of Cambridge - Nutrition - Moore, Thomas, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 559)
    - University of Cambridge - Radiotherapeutics, 1945-1949 (Box 43, Folder 560)
    - University of Cambridge - X-Ray Analysis - (Refugee, Max Perutz), 1938-1943 (Box 43, Folder 561)
    - University of Cambridge - X-Ray Analysis - (Refugee, Max Perutz), 1938-1943 (Box 43, Folder 562)
    - University of Cambridge - X-Ray Analysis - (Refugee, Max Perutz), 1938-1943 (Box 43, Folder 563)
    - University of Cambridge - X-Ray Analysis - (Refugee, Max Perutz), 1938-1943 (Box 43, Folder 564)
    - University of Cambridge - X-Ray Analysis - (Refugee, Max Perutz), 1944-1965 (Box 44, Folder 565)
    - University of Cambridge - X-Ray Analysis - (Refugee, Max Perutz), 1944-1965 (Box 44, Folder 566)
    - University of Cambridge - X-Ray Analysis - (Refugee, Max Perutz), 1944-1965 (Box 44, Folder 567)
    - University of Cambridge - X-Ray Analysis - (Refugee, Max Perutz), 1944-1965 (Box 44, Folder 568)
    - University of Cambridge - X-Ray Analysis - (Refugee, Max Perutz), 1944-1965 (Box 44, Folder 569)
    - University of Cambridge - X-Ray Analysis - (Refugee, Max Perutz), 1944-1965 (Box 44, Folder 570)
    - University of Cambridge - X-Ray Analysis - (Refugee, Max Perutz), 1944-1965 (Box 44, Folder 571)
    - University of Cambridge - X-Ray Analysis - (Refugee, Max Perutz), 1944-1965 (Box 44, Folder 572)
    - University of Cambridge - X-Ray Analysis - Reprints and Reprint Lists, 1942-1967 (Box 44, Folder 573)
    - University of Cambridge - Zoology, 1935-1939 (Box 44, Folder 574)
    - University of Cambridge - Zoology, 1962-1969 (Box 44, Folder 575)
    - University College, London - Biochemistry, 1933-1935 (Box 44, Folder 576)
    - University College, London - Chemistry, 1930-1939 (Box 44, Folder 577)
    - University College, London - Genetics, 1934-1965 (Box 45, Folder 578)
    - University College, London - Genetics, 1934-1965 (Box 45, Folder 579)
    - University College, London - Genetics, 1934-1965 (Box 45, Folder 580)
    - University College, London - Genetics, 1934-1965 (Box 45, Folder 581)
    - University College, London - Genetics, 1934-1965 (Box 45, Folder 582)
    - University College, London - Genetics, 1934-1965 (Box 45, Folder 583)
    - University College, London - Genetics, 1934-1965 (Box 45, Folder 584)
    - University College, London - Genetics, 1934-1965 (Box 45, Folder 585)
    - University College, London - Genetics, 1934-1965 (Box 45, Folder 586)
    - University College, London - Genetics, 1934-1965 (Box 45, Folder 587)
    - University College, London - Genetics, 1934-1965 (Box 45, Folder 588)
    - University College - London - Zoology and Anatomy, 1927-1933 (Box 46, Folder 589)
    - University College - London - Zoology and Anatomy, 1927-1933 (Box 46, Folder 590)
    - University College, London - Zoology - Flynn, T. T., 1933-1941, 1945-1959 (Box 46, Folder 591)
    - University College, London - Zoology - Flynn, T. T., 1933-1941, 1945-1959 (Box 46, Folder 592)
    - University of Leeds - Chemistry, 1939-1940 (Box 46, Folder 593)
    - University of Leeds - Physical Laboratory, 1934-1950 (Box 46, Folder 594)
    - University of Leeds - Physical Laboratory, 1934-1950 (Box 46, Folder 595)
    - University of Leeds - Physical Laboratory, 1934-1950 (Box 46, Folder 596)
    - University of Leeds - Physical Laboratory, 1934-1950 (Box 46, Folder 597)
    - University of Leeds - Physical Laboratory, 1934-1950 (Box 46, Folder 598)
    - University of Leeds - Physical Laboratory, 1934-1950 (Box 46, Folder 599)
    - University of Leeds - Physical Laboratory, 1934-1950 (Box 46, Folder 600)
    - University of Leeds - Physical Laboratory, 1934-1950 (Box 46, Folder 601)
    - University of Leeds - Physical Laboratory, 1934-1950 (Box 46, Folder 602)
    - University of Leeds - Physical Laboratory, 1934-1950 (Box 46, Folder 603)
    - University of Leeds - Physical Laboratory, 1934-1950 (Box 46, Folder 604)
    - University of Leeds - Physical Laboratory, 1951-1954 (Box 47, Folder 605)
    - University of Leeds - Physical Laboratory - Reports, 1943-1944; 2 items (Box 47, Folder 606)
    - University of London - Bourne, Geoffrey H. - (Visit, Histology), 1948-1950 (Box 47, Folder 607)
    - University of London - Organic Chemistry, 1938-1957 (Box 47, Folder 608)
    - University of London - Organic Chemistry, 1938-1957 (Box 47, Folder 609)
    - University of London - Organic Chemistry, 1938-1957 (Box 47, Folder 610)
    - University of London - Organic Chemistry, 1938-1957 (Box 47, Folder 611)
    - University of London - Organic Chemistry, 1938-1957 (Box 47, Folder 612)